<jobPosting><id>hubx-react-native-developer</id><company>Hubx</company><title>React Native Developer</title><url>https://hubx.co/jobs/b69c7d17b2a4-react-native-developer</url><rawText>About the job
At HubX we build mobile apps, used and loved by millions all around the world.

We have a track record of building and growing mobile apps on various verticals that reached over 200 million users across 6 continents and 170+ countries.

We are looking for a talented “React Native Developer” to join our energetic and highly motivated team.

As a talented “React Native Developer” you’d probably land an interview with many companies if you wanted to, so why choose us?

We offer you an opportunity to make a huge impact in the lives of millions of users through our products, and even the mobile app industry at large in the next years to come.

Some of your responsibilities
Create beautiful, pixel-perfect UIs across both mobile platforms that look and feel native.
Leverage native APIs for deep integrations with both platforms.
Work alongside our product owner and UI/UX designers to realize your shared vision.
Write automated tests that give us the confidence to iterate quickly and ensure the product is of the highest quality
Diagnose and fix bugs and performance bottlenecks
Engage with the React Native community to report, request, and help implement critical software fixes
Maintain a stable and current-when-possible React Native create an environment for our CI pipeline
Stay current on the latest platform capabilities so that we know whats possible
Practice Scrum with a great group of developers and product managers
What we look for
2+ years experience in mobile application development
Experience developing with React Native, Redux (Android/iOS Apps)
Experience with popular React Native workflows
JavaScript and TypeScript experience, including concepts like asynchronous programming, closures, types, and ES6
Good knowledge of CSS and HTML
Experience with REST APIs and services
Experience with unit testing
Familiarity using Scrum/Agile development methodologies
Teamwork skills with a problem-solving attitude
Practical knowledge of agile software development methodologies
Good command of written and spoken English</rawText></jobPosting>